[
  {
    "Option a": "a.Unit Testing",
    "Option b": "b.Integration Testing",
    "question": "1.Which testing is done by developer?",
    "answer": "a",
    "Option c": "c.Sanity Testing",
    "Option d": "d.Regression Testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Load Testing",
    "Option b": "b.Security Testing",
    "question": "2.Which is functional testing?",
    "answer": "c",
    "Option c": "c.Gorilla Testing",
    "Option d": "d.Benchmark Testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Evaluating deliverable to find errors",
    "Option b": "b.Finding broken code",
    "question": "3.Which term is used to define testing?",
    "answer": "a",
    "Option c": "c.A stage of all projects",
    "Option d": "d.None of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Breadth test and depth test",
    "Option b": "b.Confirmation testing",
    "question": "4.Which methodology is used to performed Maintenance testing?",
    "answer": "a",
    "Option c": "c.Retesting",
    "Option d": "d.Sanity testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Test Case",
    "Option b": "b.Requirements Traceability Matrix [RTM]",
    "question": "5.Which of the following is not part of the Test document?",
    "answer": "d",
    "Option c": "c.Test strategy",
    "Option d": "d.Project Initiation Note [PIN]"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Testing Phase",
    "Option b": "b.Requirement Phase",
    "question": "6.Which of the following is not a valid phase of SDLC (Software Development Life Cycle)?",
    "answer": "d",
    "Option c": "c.Deployment phase",
    "Option d": "d.Testing closure"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Structural testing",
    "Option b": "b.Error guessing technique",
    "question": "7.Which of the following testing is also known as white-box testing?",
    "answer": "a",
    "Option c": "c.Design based testing",
    "Option d": "d.None of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.White box and black box testing",
    "Option b": "b.White-box testing",
    "question": "8.Which of the following testing is related to the boundary value analysis?",
    "answer": "c",
    "Option c": "c.Black box testing",
    "Option d": "d.None of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Test design technique",
    "Option b": "b.Test level",
    "question": "9.Functional testing is a ------?",
    "answer": "d",
    "Option c": "c.SDLC Model",
    "Option d": "d.Test type"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Integration testing",
    "Option b": "b.Unit testing",
    "question": "10.What are the different levels of Testing?",
    "answer": "d",
    "Option c": "c.System testing",
    "Option d": "d.All of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Test type",
    "Option b": "b.Test Execution Level",
    "question": "11.Sanity testing is a ------",
    "answer": "b",
    "Option c": "c.Test Level",
    "Option d": "d.Test design technique"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Statement coverage testing",
    "Option b": "b.Decision coverage testing",
    "question": "12.White box testing techniques are?",
    "answer": "d",
    "Option c": "c.Data flow testing",
    "Option d": "d.All of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.User's end",
    "Option b": "b.Developer's end",
    "question": "13.In which environment we can performed the Alpha testing?",
    "answer": "b",
    "Option c": "c.User's and developer's end",
    "Option d": "d.None of the above"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Schedule",
    "Option b": "b.Risk",
    "question": "14.Which of the below is not a part of the Test Plan?",
    "answer": "c",
    "Option c": "c.Incident reports",
    "Option d": "d.Entry and exit criteria"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Design Errors",
    "Option b": "b.Interface Errors",
    "question": "15.What is the key objective of Integration testing?",
    "answer": "b",
    "Option c": "c.Procedure Errors",
    "Option d": "d.None of the mentioned"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Experience-based Test Design Technique",
    "Option b": "b.White Box Test Design Technique",
    "question": "16.Exploratory testing is a -----?",
    "answer": "a",
    "Option c": "c.Black Box Test Design Technique",
    "Option d": "d.Grey Box Test Design Technique"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.After the software has been modified",
    "Option b": "b.As frequently as possible",
    "question": "17.What is the best time to perform Regression testing?",
    "answer": "d",
    "Option c": "c.When the environment has been modified",
    "Option d": "d.Both option a & c"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Function testing",
    "Option b": "b.System testing",
    "question": "18.Which of the following is not part of the Test type?",
    "answer": "c",
    "Option c": "c.Statement testing",
    "Option d": "d.Database testing"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Defect Report",
    "Option b": "b.Test Summary Report",
    "question": "19.Which Test Document is used to define the Exit Criteria of Testing?",
    "answer": "d",
    "Option c": "c.Test Case",
    "Option d": "d.Test Plan"
  },
  {
    "Option a": "a.Exit Criteria",
    "Option b": "b.How much regression testing should be done?",
    "question": "20.Which testing technique is used for usability testing?",
    "answer": "b",
    "Option c": "c.Different Tools to perform Regression Testing",
    "Option d": "d.How many more test cases need to write?"
  }
]